sadhguru.org 2010-11-21

# Copyright & Privacy Policy | News

**Copyright Information and Privacy Policy (updated 05/02/10)**

This is the website of Isha Foundation. Our postal address is: 

**India:**  
Isha Foundation  
15, Govindasamy Naidu Layout, Singanallur  
Coimbatore - 641 005, INDIA

**United States:**  
Isha Foundation, Inc.   
951 Isha Lane,   
McMinnville, TN 37110 USA

Email us at [info@ishafoundation.org](mailto:info@ishafoundation.org). 

Telephone us at 866-424-ISHA, or at the numbers provided on our [Contact Us](http://www.ishafoundation.org/ContactUs) page.

**Copyright Information**

Isha Foundation is the owner of, and reserves all rights to, all material published on this website, including audio, video, electronic, multimedia, photographic, and written forms.

You may not copy, reproduce, sell, publish, display, transmit, distribute, perform, modify, create works derivative of, or in any way exploit any material from this website without the express written consent of Isha Foundation.

Requesting permission: To request permission for reprinting, publishing, licensing, or for any other use of any material or works on this website, write to Isha Foundation at the postal address provided above. Provide in writing the following information: your name (and title); the name, postal and email addresses, and telephone numbers of your organization; the mission and purpose of your organization; similar information for any other relevant contact persons in your organization; a detailed description of the material for which you are requesting permission, and where it is located on our website; and a detailed description of your intention and purpose of use of the material (how and why it will be used, published, and distributed).

Isha Foundation reserves the right to deny or withdraw permission, for any reason, for use of any material published on this website.

**Privacy Policy**

Isha Foundation does not sell or share email addresses and personal information of visitors to other companies or organizations.

Our Web host's server automatically recognizes only the domain name, but not the individual email address, of visitors to our website.

Isha Foundation collects from visitors to our website their domain name (but not the individual email address), aggregate information on the Web pages that they access or visit, and information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey responses and registrations. (The individual email addresses of those who send us email are available to us, but these are used only for the purpose specified in the email communication.)

The information we collect is used for internal review in order to improve the content and layout of our website, to customize the content and/or layout of website for individual visitors, and to notify visitors about updates to our website. This information is not shared with, or sold to, other organizations for commercial or other purposes.

We use cookies to store visitors' preferences, to record activity at the website in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, to ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same ads, and to customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

If you do not want to receive email from us, let us know by writing to us at the above email address. Please specify NO EMAIL in your email subject.

**On-line Communications:** If you provide us with your postal address on-line, you will receive only the information that you specify. If you provide your telephone number on-line, you will receive telephone contact only regarding orders you have placed (or registrations) on-line. 

Isha Foundation reserves the right to change our policy regarding how visitor information is used. If our information usage policy changes, the changes will be posted here. We will use for the new purposes only data collected after the policy change. If you are concerned about how your information will be used, check this privacy policy for changes when you visit our website.

Upon written request, we will provide you with the information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about you. Consumers can request this information by writing to the email address or postal address provided above.

**Security:**

When we request certain types of sensitive information, such as health or financial information, they will be performed using a secure server. Other transactions regarding sensitive information will also be performed using a secure server. 

If you feel that this website is not following this privacy policy, you may contact us at the addresses or telephone numbers provided above.

**Refund policy for online donations & magazine subscriptions:**

Donations and Subscriptions made online will not be refunded under any circumstances whatsoever.
